thanks to you here Georgie we love both
served
now to our fifth honoree of the night it
will be Mr Pierre Michelle
Anthony Luciano who's the current mayor
of Southern Hills Ohio
[Applause]
that'll work
absolute privilege to be a part of this
evening's
agenda here at the Cleveland
International Hall of Fame but it has
absolute honor
to be presenting
my friend and here who's Adam
to such a distinguished crowd
right here in Cleveland Ohio
the greatest location in the Nations we
did
I didn't know what I was gonna spit I've
been going over this in my head for like
three hours
anyhow I don't say that lightly it is
the greatest location
you know we have the best of all worlds
here in my opinion
let me just give you a second
we have a bit of Midwestern charm people
come here from all over the world from
another state where another County and
they come to Cleveland and you get a
whoa whoa and you Cleveland will you
know firsthand you're going to say hey
check out these great restaurants check
out all the offer and boy do we have an
offer a lot everyone's welcome here
you know we have three professional
sports teams we have a world-class 2 a
world-class Museum
world-class Orchestra
a vibrant downtown and so many other
neighborhoods that within the 20-minute
drive in any direction you can see taste
the whole world it's truly something
exceptional
but the secret sauce the secret sauce
that makes all that magic happen
is the Multicultural
background
of this community you know here
Cleveland International Hall of Fame
anywhere you look I'll talk about the
120 different evidence groups
that is the secret sauce
we are here tonight to hire a special
people
who made a significant and Lasting
contribution to our Multicultural
Society but also for those who Inspire
new generational leaders to follow those
footsteps
here at the Chinese embodiment
of this mission
and he could be we would be just in
recognizing this evening
for his contributions to just the
Lebanese community in the Middle East
community in general
but the story was not anywhere but we
wouldn't
Pierre is a champion
of diversity and harm and empowerment
wherever he goes his life Works our
Testament
to embracing others
he
built Bridges Embraces all those
different ethnic cultural and religious
backgrounds make up their secret sauce
he could not accomplished
please accomplishing his life and I'll
get over the accomplishments in a second
without the support of his family no one
if they do not have a Bedrock of her
family to support them and accomplish
great things in life
so I'd like to acknowledge his family
just a little bit Pierre was the
firstborn of four children of Elias
genre
Pierre is here tonight with his lovely
wife Mary whom they've been married 30
years
yeah about the proud parents of Julia
I'll see you with us tonight
and I know that number one support too
his brother chappie and his sister
Pauline and three of her children joined
us from overseas tonight
he has another one who's in Lebanon
brother Fanny
his grandfather
was the mayor of his hometown in Lebanon
for over 50 years
his grandfather was a tremendous
influence on Peter's life introducing to
many diplomats or politicians over his
life this is where Pierre marked his
enviable ability to communicate or
interact with any person who crosses
this path including U.S presidents
Congress governors
right down to the person standing next
to him in the grocery store
Pierre is the managing director and the
second
executive of the Region's largest Arabic
English newspaper profiling news
the senior partner and diversity
advertising agency
been recognized by global Cleveland
the American nationalism
cranes magazine
it's a recipient of trampolines award
for the Arab American foundation in
Washington DC
he's also the president of Cameo
Cleveland American Middle Eastern
organization strong supporter of our
Arts Community served on the board of
Clinton culture and Foundation
Garden Foundation is
founder and chamber of the American
public East Community Council which
promotes Lebanese Heritage and
traditions
he's also on the advisory committee for
the Cleveland Public theater
and was instrumental in developing the
Arabic theater he's also served at our
world of renowned Cleveland Museum of
Art
thank you
I want to share a little story this
family sharing with me because of fits
in so perfectly
and it was a telling of something to
come
when Pierre was in elementary school his
teacher asked his fellow students what
they want to be when they grow up
one student said I want to be a teacher
another engineer the third city was
going to be a doctor others said four
fireman scientists Etc one of his Bear's
turn he stood up teacher said Pierre
what do you want to be when you grew up
if you're allowed to fight I want to be
king
but Pierre has fulfilled his wish to be
having a sense that of the traditional
sense that an inherited a position or in
rules a country there's other
definitions of
hurricane one is chief of one
competitors another is the definition of
a king on the chess board the peace
that's able to move forwards backwards
left and right
and
he exemplifies that and I'll get to that
back a person that's able to move
forward backward left and right
a little story
when I first met here we exactly didn't
hit it off we're two leaders sharing for
a sane voice
in a small community all for the right
reasons
but I'll tell you what
it didn't end that way and short time
you're about the bridge and I walked
across that bridge and after a couple
months I did a couple meetings and went
to a couple functions
starts
here the strong leader for his family
and his community
and I said wow
that's how I want to be I don't want to
be strong for my family and my community
and from that point we were friends
but the story did not end there
neither were frankly started doing
things together
and we got lots of various functions
around town from Slavic Village to tree
my opportunity to aging time to
Collingwood out the Shaker Square and
over to Little Italy when I found
Pierre was accepted everywhere
but more importantly
he accepts all the different cultures
and after learning this and becoming his
friend and traveling around these
communities and all these different
events and all these different active
backgrounds and experiencing all these
different cultures we were number one
with friends
we were family he was abroad
put it in there
we kept going and I found him to be a
proponent of everything Greater
Cleveland by extension Ohio
and by this definition
he was okay
and what I mean is he would build a
bridge
just like the piece on the chessboard
whether he had to go back forward left
or right
he has the passion and ability to build
the bridge to all the different
Multicultural aspects of our wonderful
City
by this definition is every word
every evening
okay amongst our people
without further Ado ladies and gentlemen
please welcome my brother and arms
here in China culture
[Applause]
well I don't know what else to say
how did you get the story about me and
like
in my uh
that I wanted the best through everybody
speaks about it till now
that all my classmates they wanted to be
different and I wanted to be king and it
just
that's a dream yeah tears to my eyes
thank you Jonah
foreign
this is a great introduction
these are Beyond kind words these are
really words from the heart
and I know
you are
not only a friend of the family
you're a great great great great support
I have been a privilege to know you
not only at the mayor of Seven Hills
where I have resided for over 25 years
that also has a great leader
for the city of Southern Hills
and the surrounding region
with the foresight to think
outside the box
to improve our communities
and you do it with the utmost for
Simplicity thank you thank you
yes yes communities
and you do it with the utmost
authenticity thank you thank you
uh
too quick I have a bunch of other groups
from the community here and I apologize
for being spent out we are supposed to
be in the same area
but uh I don't know something went wrong
with the with the distribution but I
apologize for you my uh my fellow people
the my fellow community
thank you
especially thanks
to Bishop my listening thank you Bishop
for your beautiful
also
a special thing you
to our communication here tonight
have
a father is
thank you
father George Haddad from San Diego
same as well
and we're supposed to have
the Imam Imam around this Islam movie I
guess they didn't make it but he was
pleased with us thank you Imam
[Applause]
I am humbled and honored to be inducted
into the Cleveland International Hall of
Fame
especially
during the months of April
as we celebrate this month
as African American Heritage months
it is with the great right to be
inducted in this year class
of very well
deserving and that is
I have had the privilege
of knowing and working with several of
you
pray your leaders and that is
also included people I considered
mentors
who paved the way to me
to stand here tonight and view up here
every Nina and that the world thank you
uh
the famous Lebanese philosopher and
Poets
once said
he who denies his Heritage has no
heritage
[Music]
I just want to protect Mr sudasha the
Lebanese and The Phoenician created the
alphabetes
so uh
so I know my grandfather
my grandfather
so I called you too
in Lebanese
he wasn't the mega that my hometown
for over 50 years
and the president of the mayor's
associations in Montana
I was his first grandchild
and this island has shaped me into the
person I Have Become
my grandpa was a powerful shared
conscientious and respected man
most political and elected official
needed is a blessing including
presidents
and I was always by his side
deceiving many dignitaries and world
leaders when they come to Lebanon
one treasured memory
was when the Emperor of Ethiopia what is
my attention
[Music]
I want to try it
who will welcome him and greeted him
next to Grandpa
my grandpa left this Earth a few years
ago but his memory
and influence
foreign
he always told me to be humble
and respectful to everyone
no matter who you are
gender will be very proud
to see this introduction tonight
I started this journey to make a
difference
and to elevate
the respect
and understanding
of the Lebanese and Arabic communities
it has become a mission and the Daily
Progress
and innovating and improving the
preconceived notions of our community
and creating an understanding within
different cultures
we still have a long way to go
the Transformations continues
like
ICC win
Cleveland Liberty
and many other organizations
with individuals who are trying to
connect
these diverse groups in the great city
and county
getting to know many of these dedicated
individuals
has been a privilege
and I am grateful for all you you have
taught me about your conscience
I have learned
that with as many of the
the similarities I thought we had
we are much more alive than different
when I think about Society I see a very
driven that flows
Through Time
each of our cultures
feels into the river
and can make such an impact
that we can change the course
of the river's outcome
each of us is responsible
for feeding into the river to change its
course
to show the world our vibrant ethnicity
and really characteristics that make
Cleveland
this place we call home so beautiful
I can't thank you enough
for all of you here tonight attending
and celebrating this milestone in my
journey with me
your presence here tonight means the
world to me
especially to my family
who traveled from across the globe
my sister Colleen
my brother Shafi
my niece is
and my nephew
entered
thank you for being with me and sharing
this with us
thank you to my friends who also came
from across the United States
I have my friend Joe thank you Joe and
my friend also my my order thank you
thank you for traveling so much else to
be here
this journey wouldn't have been possible
without the support and understanding of
my wife for over 30 years amen thank you
our beautiful daughter Julian is the
purpose of my living and success
the support of my community
was pivotals and helping me proceed
with different projects
and the presentations in our community
and I am forever grateful for the
many friends and Community leaders I
have developed during my time and many
are here tonight thank you
thank you to the Chiefland International
Hall of Fame
and the nominating committee for
choosing a big thank you to the answers
for putting on this great event to
celebrate Cleveland's most profound
cultural leaders
I am and will continue to be
eternally grateful for this hour thank
you I have one more note
tomorrow night all of you are invited
as family president
we're having our annual start dinner
tomorrow night at cibiana restaurant in
Westlake all of you are welcome to come
and share with us and our brothers and
sisters the Muslim Community
thank you so much